fedsmith.com 2019-05-08

# Privacy Policy : FedSmith.com

We use Ezoic to provide personalization and analytic services on this website, as such Ezoic's privacy policy is in effect and can be reviewed [here](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/fedsmith.com).  

FedSmith Inc. is committed to our users’ privacy. We handle information submitted to us from our users with care. By visiting and using the FedSmith Inc. web site, you agree to the terms stated in this privacy policy.

### Personal information we collect from our users

FedSmith Inc. will collect personal information from our users from time to time. Examples of personal information that FedSmith Inc. collects includes names, email addresses, agencies, and titles of our users. This information is collected at different times through forms on our web site, such as when users sign up for our mailing list.

### Does FedSmith.com ever give my personal information out to third parties?

No. FedSmith Inc. does not disclose the personal information of our users to another party. We do not rent or sell our mailing list to other businesses or individuals. We securely store and use your personal information solely for correspondence between us and our users. We may from time to time send a sponsored newsletter to our mailing list on topics we believe would be of interest to our subscribers.

### Posting comments from our users

Some parts of the FedSmith Inc. web site are interactive, meaning our users can submit comments and information to share with other site visitors. The comments sections on our articles and our surveys offer users this capability. All comments posted to our web site can be done so anonymously. Any additional personal information a user chooses to submit when posting comments is done so at his/her own discretion and is his/her sole responsibility.

### Technical/Site usage information collected

FedSmith Inc. collects information about our site visitors whenever they view our site, such as IP addresses, browsers and operating systems used, the full uniform resource locator (URL) to, through, and from our site, and cookies. This information is used by FedSmith Inc. for statistical/tracking purposes only. Cookies are used to remember our visitors for offering custom features such as remembering a user’s title and agency on the article comments submission forms. FedSmith Inc. only stores insensitive information in cookies to ensure security. Third parties may be placing and reading cookies or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on the FedSmith.com web site.

“Cookies” are data sent to your web browser from a web server (such as Google) that can uniquely identify your computer and store information about user preferences. Most web browsers will accept cookies by default, but they can be set to reject cookies, either from all websites or from specific sites. You can also manually delete cookies from your web browser. These options are generally set through a “Privacy” setting in your browser setup.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
